Don't let Lily's death be in vain!
We need to strike while the target's eyes are still-
No way...
During the Pre-Impossible Mission Training
You're demons! Fiends!
Have you no compunctions about turning
your own teammate into a bomb?!
Look, we're sorry.
It was a good idea, though, right?
Whenever we put on some weak-ass act,
he sees right through us.
Instead, we planted the bomb on you
without telling you
and waited for the two of you to be alone.
That's when we made my special
chili bomb go kablooey!
The plan was for it to slow him down
long enough for us all to pummel him.
And hey, usin' people without their knowledge
is a tactic we could use in real fights.
It failed spectacularly, but still...
Well, our casualties were catastrophic!
I guess we needed something even more unexpected.
We could have Lily fistfight the target
on a dried-up riverbed,
then set off the bomb right as they go
for a conciliatory handshake.
We could have Lily confess her love to him,
then set off the bomb the moment
they exchange a kiss.
We could send Lily out in the dead of winter
to look for a lost puppy,
then set off the bomb when the target hugs her
to warm up her frozen shoulders.
Why's it always me getting sacrificed?!
You don't sound sorry at all!
Is there even really a point to this training?
Is it actually gonna make me stronger?
I still don't know how much I can trust that guy.
But at the same time...
Your big sister's gonna do her best.
SPY CLASSROOM
FILE: Pandemonium Sybilla
Is this your little brother and sister?
Yeah, the photo's from back at the orphanage.
Oh, you came from an orphanage?
Haven't been back much lately, but yeah.
Do your siblings know you're a spy?
Nah, my cover's that I'm workin' at
a detective agency out in the sticks.
When I left, I made 'em a promise
that someday, I'd be filthy rich
and we'd all be able to live together happily.
You're such a nice girl, Sybilla.
Wh-what're you talkin' about?!
I totally misunderstood you.
All this time, I thought you were just
a rude, uncivilized orangutan.
You wanna take that comment back?
But it turns out, you're secretly
a really kind orangutan!
You didn't take back shit!
Let's make this Impossible Mission a success!
Then, we'll get a fat bonus!
For sure.
But first things first, we gotta take that punk down!
Yeah!
And with that, let's get this strategy meeting started!
Annette says she's got some good news to share.
I've been monitoring Bro's communications, yo!
He's going into town today to pick up
a top-secret document from a collaborator!
This is the perfect chance for us to steal it!
Once we do...
Teach will be at such a loss, he'll surrender!
We can beat him without ever
having to get in a fight!
That makes sense.
That's not a bad idea.
Do you have a plan?
If we need something stolen,
I'd say that's right up Sybilla's alley.
For sure.
I'll handle this one solo.
And I don't need backup, either.
That'll let me be more flexible.
Wouldn't having more people
make it easier to tail him, though?
C'mon, have a little faith.
The only way this goes south
is if there's a traitor like last time.
This is for you, Miss Sybilla.
It seems like this might take a while,
so I packed you a lunch.
Thanks.
You can all just sit tight and wait for the good news!
Lotta people out today, huh?
If I get any closer, he'll definitely make me.
Is that where the top-secret document's hidden?!
Yeesh, the guy never leaves himself open.
At this rate, he'll get back before
I have a chance to try anything.
The hell does she think she's doing?
Hey.
Wha-wha-wha?!
What the hell gives?
I said I'd handle it solo!
I just thought, better safe than sorry.
I figured I could help out from behind the scenes.
With tailing that obvious,
you're just gonna make my job harder!
Toodles.
You got no one to blame but yourself.
Wait, what the heck?!
He's eatin' lunch here, of all places?
That's odd.
Against most people, this'd be plenty close for me.
Now, what to do?
Excuse me, would you like some juice?
It's fresh-squeezed orange juice.
I-I'm so sorry!
I-I saw the box of pretty paints,
and I couldn't help myself...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I-I... I didn't...
C'mon, don't look so down.
It was just an accident-
What the...
You made her cry.
Wait, I'm the bad guy here?!
Young lady, do you like cats?
Magnificent.
Good job reacting and stopping
the pickpocket from that far away.
You did a shoddy job tailing me,
but that last bit was excellent.
So, you knew I was there all along.
Still, completing missions will
demand more speed still.
What you need is to be as quick as a thrust needle.
Is that for me?
You apologizin'?
I'm sorry for crying.
And Mister Sowing Man,
I'm sorry for getting your nice clothes wet.
I'll take you up on that drink, then.
You got a name?
I-I'm Finé.
How about I walk you home, Finé?
Dunno why you ended up taggin' along.
One thing led to another.
I wonder what all these people think we are?
We kinda look like a couple, right?
It works in our favor to be seen as one.
We attract less attention that way.
Yeah, good point.
Now, call me "Darling," Honey.
This is training too.
D-Darling...
You thought I was being serious?
You son of a...
I swear, you're fuckin' dead!
Do you two not like each other?
Nope. I try to beat him up every day,
and he keeps mercilessly turnin' the tables on me.
I've only been using one hand lately, you know.
That's the part that pisses me off the most!
It's the same with me.
Papa always says that the only reason he gets mad
is because he loves me so much.
This place looks sketchy as hell.
But hey, this could be my chance.
If I just reach over...
I'm sorry, miss!
Finé...
You let your guard down.
What was it you were so preoccupied with?
Take these.
That juice was likely poisoned.
What the hell's goin' on?
It's a thieving ring made up of children.
I've heard there are lowlifes
who gather up orphans and
force them to commit crimes.
I set up shop in the park
in hopes they would show up,
and sure enough, they took the bait.
You mean, this was your plan from the start?
I can use this to find where Finé is going.
I'm going to follow her.
I'll make sure to get your bag back while I'm at it.
Hold up!
I'm comin' too!
FILE: Pandemonium Sybilla
This is where the signal stopped moving.
So, this is the thieves' hideout?
Are you armed?
I'm fine.
I can take care of myself.
This is no good, Finé.
None of this is worth more than chump change.
I-I'm sorry, Papa!
You gotta start pulling your weight around here.
Why can't you get that through your skull?
All I wanna do is put good food
on the table for you kids.
I just love you all so damn much.
You love 'em, huh?
Huh?
Guys like you don't know the meaning of the word.
Who the hell are you two?!
Just a couple of ordinary citizens
with an ear for rumors.
We heard there was a scumbag forcing children
to steal valuables for him to sell.
You make me sound like a monster.
I'm just looking after some kids
who don't have anywhere else to go.
I teach 'em a trade, and I keep 'em clothed and fed.
I'm basically a social worker.
Ain't that right?!
Finé cried.
Huh?
All I did was reach for her,
and she started sobbin' like the world was ending.
Hey, Finé.
What the hell's this guy been doin' to you?
I bet you say the same damn thing
every time you hit her.
"I only get mad 'cuz I care about you."
"This is how I show my love."
Shut up, you!
Don't go badmouthing
other people's teaching methods!
If you think screaming and shouting's gonna
make everything go your way, think again.
I've met loads of shitbags like you in my day!
You come from the slums, don't you?
Makes sense.
That explains why you've got such a mouth on ya.
When mouthy kids start talking back to adults,
you gotta teach 'em some manners!
Stay out of this.
He's mine.
You think you can take me, girlie?
I'm code name Pandemonium...
and it's time I cleaned you out!
Take this!
Miss!
I know that pain down in my bones.
That's why...
Eat shit, kid!
That's why I decided to become a spy.
So I could change this messed-up world!
What you need is to be as quick as a thrust needle.
Quit dashing around, you little rat!
You were wide open.
What?!
Listen, that's no kid toy-
The next one won't miss.
Wh-who the fuck are you people?
A couple of ordinary citizens, like he said.
Now, shut up so we can turn you in.
Calling the cops won't do shit.
What?
I've got a friend on the force.
I'll be out of there in no time.
The only ones getting locked up here are you people.
You pointed a gun at a fine,
upstanding member of society!
You son of a...
What's the plan, girlie?
Soon, my cop buddy's gonna
put you away for attempted murder-
Are you talking about Inspector Angerer?
Because at the moment,
the Military Intelligence Department is arresting him
on charges of suspected espionage,
Ex-Captain Frisé.
H-how do you know that name?!
Is that the top-secret document?
What a pathetic man you are.
We've been rooting out an
Imperial spy's support network,
but of all the petty crooks we've turned up,
you're the pettiest of them all.
There were no signs you were holding down a job,
but to think that you were gathering up children
and making them do your dirty work.
You only got disciplinary sanctions for
that ugly bar fight you started,
but you won't be getting off that easily this time.
You can atone for your many crimes in jail.
It's no use running.
There's no one protecting you anymore.
Life as you know it is over.
The police will be here soon.
They'll make sure the children get
placed in proper institutions.
Good to hear.
We should get outta here
while the getting is good, then.
Miss?
I, um...
Thank you!
Any time!
I gotta know...
If we complete the Impossible Mission,
is it gonna save a bunch of kids?
I used to be just like Finé.
Up until I got to the orphanage,
I lived in a shitty slum
and spent my whole life
just protecting my kid siblings.
I chose to become a spy
'cuz I wanted to change this fucked-up world of ours.
Is that choice gonna lead me
to the world I want it to?
That should go without saying.
Then I gotta get stronger, huh?
There's no need to get so worked up.
Defeating that man should have shown you that.
Seeking out strength for its own sake is meaningless.
The most important thing for a spy to have
isn't a strong body,
it's a strong heart.
And you've already got one.
Someday, this nation's children will owe you a debt.
I misjudged you.
You actually are a decent teacher.
Of course I am.
I'm going to guide you all to greatness,
or my name isn't the World's Strongest.
I will say, though, I am pretty hungry.
I missed my chance to eat lunch.
I-I've got a boxed lunch, y'know.
W-Wanna share it?
I didn't actually make it myself,
the others just kinda gave it to me.
That sounds good.
I'll take you up on that.
Nice!
Let's go halvsies, then!
First things first...
You should remove the transmitter.
Isn't this the one you stuck on
so you could follow Finé?
The transmitter was there from the start.
I just happened to have a receiver that
could pick up its wavelength.
Hold it right there, bucko!
Get back here!
You used my own trick against me!
Hold on, I can explain!
Oh yeah?! Try me!
It's nice that they're having fun.
Also, quit running away!
Hey, you!
I'm sorry, Miss Sybilla.
Miss Lily told me to give you that lunchbox,
so I didn't have much of a choice.
I really didn't need you telling her that, thanks!
Get your ass back here!
Didn't you say it yourself, Sybilla?
"Usin' people without their knowledge is
a tactic we could use in real fights,"
and "We need something even more unexpected."
You were showing off by saying stuff like that.
I was just doing what I had to to defeat Teach!
Oh yeah?
W-we stuck a chili bomb in the lunchbox.
Then, I followed you super obviously so you
wouldn't figure out what we were really up to,
and when the timing was just right,
we set off the bomb.
What do you think?
It was the perfect plan, right?
You'll notice that I'm the only one
covered in chili powder right now!
Th-that's not fair!
Turnabout is fair play, so why are you so...
Wait, could it be?
Are you just mad because we were listening
to your whole conversation with Teach
so we'd know when to blow the bomb?
Gosh, you sounded so maidenly.
"I've got a boxed lunch, y'know."
It was like listening to a pair of innocent young lovers.
I tell you, we couldn't get the grins off
our faces when we heard that.
I'll just punch you 'til you forget!
It's punching time!
Nooo!
Get back here, dammit!
Deceive each other.
Trick each other.
Improve each other.
Keep at it, and you'll be strong enough
to defeat me someday.
Until then, though, the occasional
quarrel between teammates
can be magnificent too.